here I have two contracts test and port
在这里，我有两个合同测试以及灵魂和食物的移植，所有这些都在测试之内
on soul and food that's all inside test
and port I want to use the food contract
和港口我想使用食物合同，所以在此视频中，我将向您展示
so in this video I'm going to show you
two examples how to import local files
两个示例如何导入本地文件以及如何从中导入合同
and also how to import contracts from
Jacob calm now the examples I'm going to
雅各布现在冷静，我将向您展示如何导入合同的示例
show you for how to import contracts
from github only works in remix first
来自github的文件只能在混音中工作首先让我们看一下如何导入本地文件
let's go over how to import local files
you can see here that inside the browser
您可以在这里看到，在浏览器文件夹中，我们在学校进行了测试导入，
folder we have test import at school and
food Seoul and to import a solidity file
食物首尔，要导入一个坚固性文件，您首先要输入单词import，然后
you start with the word import and then
followed by the relative path to the
紧随其后的是您从食物开始要导入的文件的相对路径
file that you want to import since food
dog soul is inside the same folder as
狗的灵魂与测试导入在同一文件夹中，我们要说的是
test import here we're gonna say that
food that soul is in the current
放在句号后面的那个灵魂在当前目录中的食物
directory by putting a period followed
by a slash and then followed by the name
以斜线开头，然后以文件名命名，然后是灵魂，然后不要
of the file food uh soul and then don't
forget to put a semicolon now let's say
现在忘了放分号，让我们说那个灵魂在我的文件夹里的食物
that food that soul was inside my folder
then back here you would have to say my
然后回到这里，您将不得不说我的文件夹将食物砍了出来，一旦我们
folder slash food out soul and once we
import food out so we can use the
进口食物，以便我们可以使用此文件中的合同食物，所以在这里
contract food inside this file so here
I'll initialize a food contract and then
我将初始化一份食物合同，然后创建一个名为“获取全名”的函数
create a function called get full name
and then return the value of the state
然后返回食品合同中的状态变量名称的值
variable name inside the food contract
next I'm going to show you how to import
接下来，我将向您展示如何从github导入文件，我们将导入
files from github and we'll import the
ERC xx talking contract from the open
ERC xx正在讨论的日本公开合同中的合同，并将其导入
Japan contracts and to import this
contract we first need to copy the URL
合同，我们首先需要复制网址，然后再像之前一样从导入和
and then as before start with import and
then paste the URL and then from the URL
然后粘贴网址，然后从网址中删除HTTPS
we need to remove HTTPS
and don't forget to put the semicolon
并且不要忘了现在放分号，这样导入将无法正常工作
now this import will not work as you can
see here and the reason is because the
看到这里，原因是因为我们刚导入的坚固性是为了
solidity that we just imported is for
solidity version 0.6 and above but here
实体版本0.6及更高版本，但在这里我们使用的字面上是0.5，因此
we're working with so literally 0.5 so
what we actually want to do is import
我们实际上想要做的是导入ERC 24 solidity 0.5，我们可以做到这一点
ERC 24 solidity 0.5 and we can do that
by switching over to github branch 2
通过切换到github分支2 2.5版，您可以看到
version 2.5 and as you can see the
solidity is now 0.5 so we'll copy this
坚固性现在为0.5，因此我们将复制此URL，然后放置此URL，然后
URL and then we place this URL and then
again we move the HTTP and when you hit
再次，我们移动HTTP，当您按ctrl进行编译时，您会注意到
ctrl s for compile you'll notice that
solidity compile and now we can create
编译，现在我们可以创建自己的ERC 20令牌，因此我将其命名为
our own ERC 20 token so I'll name this
ERC 20 token my token and it's gonna
ERC 20令牌是我的令牌，它将扩展我们刚刚使用的ERC 20令牌
extend that ERC 20 token that we just
imported from here and when you deploy
从这里导入，以及在部署合同时测试导入我的令牌
the contracts test import my token
you'll notice that get foo name returns
您会注意到get foo name返回foo，这是状态的值
foo which is the value of the state
variable here and we imported ERC 20
这里的变量，我们从github导入了ERC 20令牌并创建了我们自己的
token from github and created our own
SB 20 token and you can see here all of
SB 20令牌，您可以在此处看到IRC 20令牌的所有功能，因此
the functionalities of IRC 20 token so
I'll show you how to import contracts
我将向您展示如何从github上的本地文件和合同导入合同
from local files and contracts on github
and knowing how to import contracts from
知道如何从github导入合同到remix是一个有用的技巧
github into remix is a useful trick to
remember when you want to quickly test
记得当您想快速测试合同时，在下一个视频中见
out contracts see you in the next video
and have a nice weekend
周末愉快